Becca: Hi, it’s me … Becca.
Dave: Hi. It’s the first floor.
Come in.
Becca: Great flat, Dave.
Dave: Do you like it? It has nice kitchen.
Becca: Mmm. Nice smell.
Er, where’s Dolly?
Dave: Dolly isn’t here.
Em, Becca, I need to tell you something.
Dolly isn’t my dog.
She’s my friend’s dog.
I sometimes help and take her for a walk.
Becca: You don’t have a dog?
Dave: No. I don’t like dogs much.
And my flat’s quite small.
So sorry. I know you love dogs.
Becca: Don’t worry!
Barry isn’t my dog either!
He’s my sister’s dog. I like dogs, but… in fact… I have two cats.
How do you feel about cats?
Dave: I love cats – in fact I prefer cats to dogs!
Sit down. It’s nearly ready.
Becca: What’s for lunch?
Dave: Pizza – and then chocolate ice cream.
All home-made!
Becca: All for me this time!